Anywhere you are, distance is not a barrier.
Viewers, you are called to battle spiritual entities which cause crisis in your lives.
You and Prophet T.B Joshua together in the name of Jesus can stop satan from killing, stealing and destroying
your life. Touch the screen right now. Engage with God.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are,
whatever challenges, whatever situation you are in -
be released in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever you are, whatever situation you are in -
be released in the name of Jesus!
Whatever situation you are in, whatever challenges -
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I release your business in the name of Jesus!
I release your business from setback in the name of Jesus.
I release your business from collapsing in the name of Jesus!
Your finances, be anointed in the name of Jesus!
I anoint your finances in the name of Jesus!
Be restored!
Your finances, be restored!
Your business, be restored in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Your health, whatever challenges in your blood, in your fluid, in your tendons, in your muscles,
in your bones and all your faculties - be restored in the name of Jesus!
Be cured!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Say: "I am cured, in the name of Jesus!"
I am cured, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever poison you might have eaten through dreams,
from the table of your enemy - be flushed out by the blood of Jesus!
Be flushed out by the blood of Jesus!
You fibroid, be flushed out by the blood of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power in our generation today;
and stay up to date with the latest prophesies, deliverances, service, and testimonies.
From the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world
RV: Juliet Bwalya 02/07/2018